Finding aid for Media Resources Center (University of Michigan) Films and Videotapes, 1930s and 1948-1987
Bentley Historical Library
- Series AF - Archives Film
  - Students Looking at Peace Corps Plaque, 1964; [851831-AF-162]; (UM students looking at plaque on Michigan Union commemorating President Kennedy's announcement of the Peace Corps. Good close-up of the plaque.)
    - Original:, 16mm film,; wp, col, sil, 100; 100
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, col, sil,102, 00:02:53
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 3)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-AF162.flv
  - UM Fresh Air Camp, 1964; [851831-AF-163]; (Footage from the UM camp for delinquent boys includes shots of boys and counselors at various camp activities.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos; wp, col; col, sil; sil, 200; 200
  - Rocket Launch, circa 1964; [851831-AF-164]; (Footage from the UM rocket launch site shows rocket launcher, data recording equipment, launch crew and VIP observers, loading of the rocket, and a rocket launch.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, col, sil, 576, 00:16:03
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 3)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-AF164.flv
  - Music School Dedication, Sept. 1964, [851831-AF-165]; (Footage of the dedication ceremony at new Music Building includes presentation of awards to Eileen Saarinen, Leonard Bernstein, Aaron Copeland and others, some footage of Bernstein and Copeland conducting UM orchestra, views of building and grounds. Features: Harlan Hatcher, UM-Pres.; Eileen Saarinen, Leonard Bernstein, Aaron Copeland, Charles Sink)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos; wp, col; col, sil; sil; at, 100; 100
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, col, sil, 554, 00:15:25
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 2)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-AF165.flv
  - Football, 1964, Purdue cutaways, [851831-AF-166]; (Cutaways of crowd and players at UM-Purdue football game. Good footage of UM Marching band in formation, Victor Borge hamming it up in the press box. (On core with #168,170)Features: Marching Band; Victor Borge)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, col, sil; at, 200
  - Faculty Awards, 1964-1965; 1964; [851831-AF-167]; (Presentation of Faculty Awards, includes footage of Pres. Hatcher speaking and the award ceremony. Features: Harlan Hatcher, UM-Pres.; Reed Nesbit, UM-Med.; Peter Gosling, UM-Geog.; Norman Thomas, UM-Pol.; Kenneth Boulding, UM-Econ; Caesar Blake, UM-Engl.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos; pos, col; col, sof; sof; at, 500; 545
  - Sargent Shriver, Director of the Peace Corps, 1964; [851831-AF-168]; (Shriver talks to a large crowd of students outside Michigan Union at the site of a plaque commemorating President Kennedy's announcement of the Peace Corps. (On core with #166, 170.)Features: Harlan Hatcher, UM-Pres.; Sargent Shriver)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp; wp, col; col, sil; sil; at, 98, 98
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, col, sil, 98, 00:02:48
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 2)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-AF168.flv
  - Aeronautical Engineering 50th Anniversary, 1964; [851831-AF-169]; (Footage of recipients of honorary degrees at ceremonies marking the 50th anniversary of instruction in aeronautical engineering at the University of Michigan. Honorees are UM alums who distinguished themselves in aeronautical or aerospace engineering. Features: William Hawkins; Allen Donovan; James Dempsey)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, col, sil, 100
  - George Lincoln Rockwell Protests, 1964; [851831-AF-170]; (Pickets and rally protesting appearance of American Nazi Party leader George Lincoln Rockwell at Hill Auditorium. Filmed at night outside Hill Auditorium. (On core with #166, 168.))
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, color, sil, 77, 00:02:09
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 2)
    - Streaming File:
  - Homecoming 1964, [851831-AF-171]; (Footage of Homecoming activities including the "mudbowl," a tug-of-war across the Huron River, fraternity and sorority displays and sculptures, and a soap-box derby. (On reel with #173.))
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, col, sil, 391, 00:11:02
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 2)
    - Streaming File:
  - Ohio State Football Game Rally, 1964, [851831-AF-173]; (Rally on the Diag before the football team left for Columbus to play Ohio State, including shots of President Hatcher and Coach Elliot. Also footage of the arrival of the victorious team at Willow Run airport. (On reel with #171)Features: Harlan Hatcher, UM-Pres.; Charles "Bump" Elliot, UM-Ath.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp, col, sil; at, 200
  - 1965 Blizzard, [851831-AF-174]; (Footage taken during and after a severe snowstorm. Campus scenes of snow removal, cars on unplowed streets, students walking through snow to Angell Hall. (120 foot version is on core with #186-189.))
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos; pos, col; col, sil; sil, 80; 120
  - Alumni Luncheon (late 1950s?), [851831-AF-175]; (Footage of an alumni awards luncheon includes the Emeritus Club awards ceremony, the luncheon, a meeting of Medical Alumni, and several alumni from the class of 1911. (Total of 3 negative and 3 work prints.)Features: Harlan Hatcher, UM-Pres.; Edward R. Murrow)
    - Original:, 16mm film, neg; wp, b/w; b/w, sil; sil, 1000; 1000
  - USPH Pollution Laboratory, 1965; [851831-AF-176]; (Footage of the signing of an agreement between the University of Michigan and the United States Public Health Service to build a Water Pollution Laboratory. (Copyright held by USPHS.))
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, col, sil, 100
  - Navy-Michigan Football Game, 1964, [851831-AF-177]; (Complete footage of the Michigan's 21-0 football victory over the Naval Academy and most of the half-time band show. (Three reels of film, two of game and one of band show and cutaways. Two reels of magnetic sound track, 6 reels audio tape.)Features: Marching Band)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos; pos; pos, col; col; col, sof; sof; sof; sot, 2000
  - Institute of Science and Technology Dedication, 1964; [851831-AF-178]; (Footage from the open house during the dedication of the IST building on North Campus, includes good shots of equipment, displays and laboratories.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, col, sil, 100
  - Music School, circa 1964; [851831-AF-179]; (Good footage of the exterior of the new Music School building and the reflecting pond.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, col, sil,102, 00:02:51
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 2)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-AF179.flv
  - Campus Scenes from "Idea of Michigan" Trims, 1960; [851831-AF-180]; (Footage shot for the film "Idea of Michigan." Includes shots of Burton Tower, Rackham Building, Health Services, women's dormitories, Frieze Building, Phoenix Memorial Lab, and the President's House. (On core with #182.))
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, col, sil, 100
  - Salk Vaccine Announcement, 1955, 1958; [851831-AF-181]; (Film of press conference in Rackham Auditorium prior to announcing successful test of the Salk polio vaccine. Dr Francis and Dr. Salk talk about the development of the vaccine and testing methods. Features: Thomas Francis Jr., UM-SPH; Jonas Salk, E. Van Ryper, David Bodian, Thomas Rivers, Basil O'Connor)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, b/w, sof, 1064, 00:29:42
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 2)
    - Streaming File:
  - Great Lakes Core Sampling, [851831-AF-182]; (Footage of a Great Lakes Research Institute research vessel taking core samples from bottom of one of the Great Lakes. Close-ups of men working the drilling equipment on board ship. (On core with #180.))
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos; pos, col; col, sil; sil, 200; 200
  - Midyear Graduation, Jan. 1965, 1964; [851831-AF-183]; (Footage of commencement speaker Thurgood Marshall in conversation with unidentified man and of President Hatcher in informal discussions. (On core with #185, film has a blue tint.)Features: Harlan Hatcher, UM-Pres.; Thurgood Marshall)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, col, sil, 45, 00:01:19
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 2)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-AF183.flv
  - Ohio State - Michigan Basketball, 1965, [851831-AF-184]; (Footage of the Michigan - Ohio State basketball game, cutaways of the band performing, and of the presentation of the football player of the year award to Bob Timberlake. Features: Bob Timberlake, Football Player of The Year)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos; wp, col; col, sil; sil, 300; 300
  - League Anniversary Plaque, 1965; [851831-AF-185]; (Several shots of plaque by front door of Michigan League--commemorates anniversary of the building. Women posing by plaque are not identified, except blonde girl is Nancy Freitag, League Pres., 1964-65. Features: Nancy Freitag, League Pres., 1964-65)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, col, sil, 60
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, color, sil, 83, 00:02:22
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 2)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-AF185.flv
  - Civil Rights Rally, 1965; [851831-AF-186]; (Footage of a civil rights march and rally on the UM campus and in downtown Ann Arbor, apparently in support of civil rights activities in Selma, Alabama. (One copy on core with #187-189.))
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, col, sil, 98
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, col, silent, 98, 00:02:47
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 2)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-AF186.flv
  - Michigan - Minnesota Basketball Game, 1965, [851831-AF-187]; (Film clips from Michigan's 88-85 basketball win over Minnesota. (On cores with #184 and #186-189.))
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos; pos, col; col, sil; sil, 340; 340
  - Marina Oswald, 1965; [851831-af -188]; (Footage of Marina Oswald, widow of Kennedy assassin Lee Harvey Oswald, receiving diploma from the director of the English Language Institute. (One on core with #186-189.) (Needs repair.)Features: Marina Oswald; John Catford, UM-ELI)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp; wp, col; col, sil; sil
  - Big Ten Wrestling, Spring 1965, [851831-AF-189]; (Footage of UM wrestling match, shots of wrestling coach Cliff Keen. Filmed at Yost Field House. Features: Clifford Keen, UM-Wrestling Coach)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos.wp, col; col, sil; sil, 135; 135
  - Vietnam Teach-In, 1965; [851831-AF-190-a]; (Coverage of crowds and speakers on the Diag and first Vietnam War Teach-In held in Mason Hall at the University of Michigan, interviews Eric Wolfe and William Gamson, two of the organizers (Dupe neg. from B wind reversal shot by WXYZ, Ch. 7 Detroit.)Features: William Gamson, UM-Soc.; Eric Wolfe, UM-Anthro.; Bill Bonds, Ch 7 TV Newscaster)
    - Original:, at
    - Original:, 16mm film, neg, b/w, sof,371, 00:10:20
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 2)
    - Streaming File:
  - Vietnam Teach-In, 1965, [851831-AF-190-b]; (Shots of crowd in Haven Hall Lobby (Fishbowl) and in lecture hall, crowd and speakers)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, col, sil, 92, 00:02:38
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 2)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-AF190-b.flv
  - Campus Fashions, 1965; [851831-AF-191]; (On-campus shots of female legs showing many different stocking and boot styles.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, col, sil, 50
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, b/w, sil, 63, 00:01:50
    - Streaming File:, 851831-AF191.flv
  - Honors Convocation, Spring 1965, [851831-AF-192]; (Exterior views of robed dignitaries leaving President's House, getting into limos. Also shots of Pres. Hatcher and guests inside President's House. Features: Harlan Hatcher, UM-Pres.; Prince Bernhard of the Netherlands; George Romney)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, col, sil, 100
  - James Reston Press Conference, 1965; [851831-AF-193]; (James Reston and reporters in Regents' Room in the Administration Bldg. Features: James Reston, NY Times)
    - Original:, 16mm film, neg; wp, b/w; b/w, sil; sil; at, 200; 200
  - Football Practice, Basketball Semi-Finals-Regional, 1965; [851831-AF-194]; (Footage of Michigan's win over Vanderbilt in NCAA basketball regional final at Lexington, Ky., 1965. (Three reels of audiotape of the basketball game.))
    - Original:, 16mm film, b/w; col; col, b/w; col; col, sil; sil; sil; at, 100; 100; 100
  - Medical Graduation, 1965; [851831-AF-195]; (Footage of the Medical School graduation and the Hippocratic oath ceremony.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp, b/w, sill, 100
    - Original:, 16mm film, neg, b/w, sil, 100, 00:02:49
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 2)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-AF195.flv
  - Great Lakes Research Boats, Spring, 1965., [851831-AF-196]; (Long and close-up shots of 3 UM boats, all taken in 1 day on Lake Mich. and in Grand Haven Harbor. Shots of men working with equipment, dredge, sample bottles, interior shots of boat, underwater TV (?) Boats are Inland Seas, Mysis, Highland Lassie.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos; wp, col; col, sil; sil, 1060
  - Graduation, 1965, [851831-AF-197]; (Presentation of honorary degrees at 1965 graduation ceremony. (2 reels of audiotape, sof is of poor quality.)Features: Harlan Hatcher-UM Pres., James Reston, NY Times)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp; pos, col; col, sil; sil, 300
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, color, sof, 952, 00:26:30
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 2)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-AF197.flv
  - Astronauts, Space Research Laboratory Dedication, 1965; [851831-AF-198-a]; (Astronauts filmed at the Airport, UM Stadium. Also footage of the Dedication of the UM Space Research Laboratory. (There are four reels of magnetic sound track and 3 reels of audiotape to accompany this title.)Features: Pres. & Mrs. Hatcher, Governor and Lenore Romney, James McDivitt and spouse, Edward White and spouse.)
    - Original:, sot; at, 1000
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, color, silent, 798, 00:22:10
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 3)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-AF198-a.flv
  - Astronauts, Space Research Laboratory Dedication, 1965; [851831-AF-198-b]; (Footage of Edward White's Address given at the Honorary Degree Awards in UM Stadium. Features: Harlan Hatcher, UM-Pres.; Edward White, Astronaut; James McDivitt, Astronaut.)
    - Original:, sot
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, color, sof, 1172, 00:33:19
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 3)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-AF198-b.flv
  - Astronauts, Space Research Laboratory Dedication, 1965; [851831-AF-198-c]; (Astronauts being greeted at Airport, reception line. (NASA plane.)Features: Pres. & Mrs. Hatcher; Gov. and Lenore Romney; James McDivitt and spouse, Edward White and spouse)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp, col, sil
  - Astronauts, Space Research Laboratory Dedication, 1965; [851831-AF-198-d]; (Astronauts at commencement, presentation of Honorary Degrees at UM Stadium)
    - Original:, 16mm film,; wp, col, sof, 200
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, color, sil, 303, 00:08:27
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 3)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-AF198-d.flv
  - Astronauts, Space Research Laboratory Dedication, 1965; [851831-AF-198-e]; (Dedication of Aerospace Engineering Building, North Campus. Features: James McDivitt, Astronaut; Edward White, Astronaut, Dr. Thompson, NASA; Dr. Webb, NASA)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, col, sof, 404, 00:11:19
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 3)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-AF198-e.flv
  - Astronauts, Space Research Laboratory Dedication, 1965; [851831-AF-198-f]; (Footage of Astronaut Edward White speaking at commencement in UM Stadium, talks of his UM background and the quality of his education at Michigan. Features: Edward White, Astronaut)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, color, sof
  - Astronauts, Space Research Laboratory Dedication, 1965; [851831-AF-198-g]; (Lt. Col. James McDivitt and Col. Edward White (Gemini IV) are filmed receiving honorary degrees, both address graduates, Ann Arbor High School Band plays. Features: James McDivitt, Astronaut; Edward White, Astronaut; Ann Arbor High School Band)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp, col, sof, 390
  - Astronauts, Space Research Laboratory Dedication, 1965; [851831-AF-198-h]; (Presentation of clocks to astronauts White and McDivitt, also a resolution of the state of Michigan honoring their achievement, presentation of honorary degrees. (Film has been spliced, sound is distorted.)Features: Harlan Hatcher, UM-Pres; George Romney; James McDivitt, Astronaut; Edward White, Astronaut)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, col, sof, 1200
  - Astronauts, Space Research Laboratory Dedication, 1965; [851831-AF-198-I]; (Interview of Astronauts McDivitt and White at reflecting pool of School of Music. Features: James McDivitt, Astronaut; Edward White, Astronaut)
    - Original:, 16mm film, col, sof, 1114, 00:30:59
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 3)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-AF198-i.flv
  - Winter Weekend, 1965, [851831-AF-199]; (Ice sculpture and cheering contest by students on Ferry Field. Hazel Losh acts as judge. Features: Hazel Losh, UM-Astron.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp, col, sil; at, 300
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, col, sil, 300, 00:08:24
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 3)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-AF199.flv
  - Pep Rally, March 1965, [851831-AF-200]; (Pep rally in Yost Field House just before NCAA basketball semi-finals. Speeches by Pres. Hatcher, basketball coach Dave Strack, Dr. Hazel Losh, and some senior players. Pep Band. Features: Harlan Hatcher, UM-Pres.; Dave Strack, UM-Ath.; Hazel Losh, UM-Astron.; Wally Weber, UM-Ath.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, col, sil, 170
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, col, sil, 196, 00:05:29
    - Streaming File:, 851831-AF200.flv
  - Dr. Charles Sink, 1965; [851831-AF-201]; (Dr. Charles Sink, president of the University Musical Society, standing at the entrance of Hill Auditorium during a May Festival concert. Features: Charles Sink, UM-Music)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, col, sil, 32, 00:00:58
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 3)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-AF201.flv
  - Awixa Flowers, 1965; [851831-AF-202]; (Yearly Ann Arbor spring event-viewing the crabapple blossoms along whole of Awixa Street.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, col, sil, 100
  - UM Jazz, 1965; [851831-AF-203]; (Summer, 1965. UM Jazz Band filmed arriving at Airport from Latin American tour. Features: UM Jazz Band)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, col, sil, 60
  - Hawaiian Observatory, June 1965; [851831-AF-204]; (Exterior and interior shots of ARPA Mid-course Observation Station (AMOS), an astronomical observatory on Maui, Hawaii, founded by the University of Michigan as it is nearing completion. Also wide pan shots of Diamond Head.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp, col, sil, 400
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, color, sil, 498, 00:11:12
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 3)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-AF204.flv
  - Rose Bowl, 1965, [851831-AF-205-a]; (Footage of UM Marching Band in California for the 1965 Rose Bowl, includes band at practice, concert at Union Square, half-time performance at Shrine Game, San Francisco and Disneyland concerts, Rose Bowl pre-game and half-time shows. Features: Marching Band)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp; pos; wp, col; col; col, sil; sil; sil, 700; 800; 800
  - Rose Bowl, 1965, [851831-AF-205-b]; (Footage of the UM Marching Band in California for 1965 Rose Bowl Game, Parade. Features: Marching Band)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp; wp, col; col, sil; sil, 550; 550
  - Rose Bowl Football Game, 1965, [851831-AF-206]; (Press deck and field coverage of UM vs. Oregon. Good coverage of Mel Anthony's long run in 2nd quarter. (Some 2nd half footage is out of focus.)Features: Mel Anthony)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos; wp, col; col, sil; sil, 1000
  - Campus Construction, Summer 1965, [851831-AF-207]; (Shots of buildings under construction, new seats being installed in Stadium, Univ. Towers Apt. Bldg., UM Cedar Bend Housing, Bursley Hall, ISR, wrecking of house on Maynard St. (Needs repair.))
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp,col, sil, 450; 610
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, color, sil, 603, 00:16:47
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 3)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-AF207.flv
  - Princeton-Michigan Basketball, NCAA Semi-finals, 1965; [851831-AF-208]; (Official NCAA footage of Michigan vs. Princeton Basketball semi-finals. (B wind dupe negative, silent 1000 ft. from NCAA, 100 feet edited out and B wind prints made.))
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos; neg; neg, b/w; b/w; b/w, sil; sil; sil, 100; 100; 1000
  - Dean Joiner, Law School, Summer, 1965, [851831-AF-209]; (Dean Joiner speaks about preparation for the UM Sesquicentennial in 1968. (Shot in UM-TVC studio for use in 1964/65 "Perspective Michigan") (Needs repair.)Features: Charles Joiner, UM-Law)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp, b/w; sof; at, 100
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, col, sof, 168, 00:04:46
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 3)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-AF209.flv
  - House Demolition, 1965; [851831-AF-210]; (Various close-ups of wrecking of house. A UM construction site?)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos; pos, col; col, sil; sil, 75; 95
  - UM Basketball Team Leaving for Europe, 1965; [851831-AF-211]; (Various shots of UM basketball team boarding plane at airport for tour of Europe.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp; pos, col; col, sil; sil, 75; 100
  - Announcement of Allan Smith as VP for Acad Affairs, 1965; [851831-AF-212]; (Announcement of Allan Smith, UM-Law, as new VP for Academic Affairs. Portions of speech by Pres. Hatcher on the State of the University. Filmed in Regents' Room, Administration Bldg. (Footage of Smith and Heyns is silent, sof for part of Hatcher.)Features: Harlan Hatcher, UM-Pres.; Roger Heyns, UM-VP; Allan Smith, UM-Law,; Fedele Fauri, UM-SW; Tom D. Rowe, UM-Pharm.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp, col, sof; at, 700
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, col, sound,722, 00:20:03
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 3)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-AF212.flv
  - Marcos of Philippines, 1965; [851831-AF-213]; (Awarding of honorary degree to Philippine president Ferdinand Marcos. President and Mrs. Marcos leaving Rackham, arriving at President's House, receiving honorary degree in room of President's House (?)Features: Pres. and Mrs. Hatcher; Pres. and Mrs. Marcos; Gov. and Mrs. Romney)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp; wp, col; col, sil; sil, 155; 550
  - Campus, 1965, Summer and Winter Scenes, [851831-AF-213-a]; (Various shots of campus-summer and winter scenes. Includes West Engineering Arch, McDivitt/White Street Sign. Also shots of State St., Angell Hall, Burton Tower, Back of old Med Center (?), Artist's drawing of New Med Center (?))
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp; wp; col; col, sil; sil, 50; 50
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, color, sil, 254, 00:07:04
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 3)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-AF213-a.flv
  - Gemini IV, [851831-AF-214]; (Shots of Astronaut White outside the space capsule. (Duplicated from NASA film for the 1964-65 "Perspective Michigan" film.)Features: Edward White, Astronaut)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp, col, sil, 120
  - Richard Cutler, Stephen Spurr, R. F. Malcomson, 1965; [851831-AF-215]; (Richard Cutler, VP for Student Affairs, Stephen Spurr, Dean of Graduate School, Reginald F. Malcomson, Dean, School of Architecture and Design. Each is shown in front of their respective University building. Shots of Northwood Apartments. Features: Richard Cutler, UM-VP; Stephen Spurr, UM-SNR; Reginald F. Malcomson, UM-Arch.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, wp; wp, b/w; col, sil; sil, 235; 270
  - Vietnam Conference, Summer 1965, [851831-AF-216]; (Filmed at the time of the conference in Hill Auditorium and Mason Hall, at night. Includes shots of D.C. Baldwin, Head of Office of Religious Affairs. Features: DeWitt C. Baldwin, UM-Religious Affairs)
    - Original:, 16mm film, neg, b/w; sil, 100
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos, color, sil ,99, 00:02:38
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 3)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-AF216.flv
  - Football Cutaways, 1965, [851831-AF-217]; (Football cutaways, includes footage of stadium crowd, press box, field coach, and a panoramic view of Ann Arbor from UM Stadium.)
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos; pos, col; col, sil; sil, 50; 200
  - Faculty Awards, Winter, 1965; [851831-AF-218]; (Faculty Awards are presented. (Most of film is dark, underexposed.))
    - Original:, 16mm film, pos; pos, col; col, sil; sil, 170; 170